codenuclear.com 2018-12-19

# Privacy Policy - codeNuclear

### Disclaimer

The contents of this report are based on information generally available to the public from sources believed to be reliable. No representation is made that it is timely, accurate or complete. codeNuclear has taken due care and caution in compilation of data as this has been obtained from various sources including which it considers reliable and first hand. However, codeNuclear does not guarantee the accuracy, adequacy or completeness of any information and it is not responsible for any errors or omissions or for the results obtained from the use of such information and especially states that it has no financial liability whatsoever to the subscribers/users of this report. The information herein, together with all estimates and forecasts, can change without notice. This report does not purport to be a solicitation of any advice pertaining to trade and business and readers are advised to consult experts or study / evaluate individual business prospectus and other relevant legal documents before taking any decisions based on information provided in the site. Neither codeNuclear nor its Editors or Authors accept any liability whatsoever nor do they accept responsibility for any financial consequences arising from the use of the research or information provided herein. 

### Privacy Policy

We understand the importance of your privacy as a visitor to this website. We want you to understand how the information you may provide will be used. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. 

### Information collected

codeNuclear does not collect personal information about you except for the information that you voluntarily provide. We may collect usage information of our site to analyze interest in content and to provide advertisers information on an aggregate basis. No personally identifiable information will be shared with third-party advertising companies. 

###  Community

When using our online community functions, your email address will identify you. We encourage our users to select a unique user ID to avoid providing your email address to other users and third parties. Failure to use this feature to select a unique user ID may result in other users or third parties sending you unsolicited email. 

### Google Adsense and the DoubleClick DART Cookie

Google, as a third party advertisement vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. The use of DART cookies by Google enables them to serve adverts to visitors that are based on their visits to this website as well as other sites on the internet.

To opt out of the DART cookies you may visit the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following url <http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads> Tracking of users through the DART cookie mechanisms are subject to Google’s own privacy policies.

Other Third Party ad servers or ad networks may also use cookies to track users activities on this website to measure advertisement effectiveness and other reasons that will be provided in their own privacy policies, codeNuclear has no access or control over these cookies that may be used by third party advertisers.

### Links to third party Websites

We have included links on this site for your use and reference. We are not responsible for the privacy policies on these websites. You should be aware that the privacy policies of these sites may differ from our own.

### Changes to this Privacy Statement

The contents of this statement may be altered at any time, at our discretion.

If you have any questions regarding the privacy policy of codeNuclear then you may contact us through the contact form on Contact Us page.

Best Regards,  
The codeNuclear Team
